His heart…
Why isn't it beating?
My dad's not dead.
If I can get his Stand back,
he'll surely come back to life.
I'll tell you one thing.
That power that awakened within you…
It's called a Stand ability.
I have to go see her. Jolyne…
Jolyne Cujoh.
PUNISHMENT WARD
I see.
So Ermes has learned about Stand abilities
and about the discs too.
When Ermes inserted
McQueen's memory disc back into him,
he came back to life.
He was resuscitated.
We may be able to bring your father back
if we have his discs!
And what did you do
with this janitor's discs?
I'm keeping them safe.
I have both discs.
She said the guards would find it
during body checks
if she brought them to her cell.
I'll hold on to his Stand ability,
but I'll insert
his memory disc back later.
McQueen's memory disc.
This disc contains memories
related to Pale Snake.
And maybe
memories of Dad's discs too.
It's coming!
Hurry, shut the door!
I was only trying to change
the tractor's tire!
I barely touched it!
Hurry!
Hurry, get out of there!
We need to close this door!
Come on, help me!
Okay!
It's heavy!
Pull harder! It's almost closed.
Now, pull!
What the hell are you doing?
I said pull harder!
Those aren't my arms…
Bro!
I know.
I was the one…
who didn't pull hard enough--
EPISODE 7: THERE'S SIX OF US!
Fine weather, as always.
Tell me, Charlotte,
what is this commotion for?
Why did we call this assembly?
This afternoon,
two inmates went missing
on the farm grounds.
Is that so?
That's not good.
The prisoners could not have
escaped from the farm grounds.
They must have drowned
in the surrounding wetlands
or gotten bitten by venomous snakes.
I think we need
to assemble a search party.
Why don't you talk about the possibility
of them being eaten by a crocodile?
Maybe a female crocodile.
Who was that? What did you say?!
I did not eat them! I am innocent!
Anyways.
I have called you here
to form a volunteer search party.
You will not be compensated,
nor will your sentence get shortened.
I'd like to ask for your compassion.
Are there any volunteers?
Come on, Jolyne.
You just got out of the Punishment Ward.
Why would choose to tire yourself more?
Because you won't be there.
What?
Very well.
A party of five is plenty.
Guard, bring the usual please.
Inmates going to the farm
must wear this
on their wrists to prevent escape.
"Like a Virgin."
Also known as "invisible wall."
In trying to take the bracelet cuffs off
you give it impact,
or if it breaks,
it will explode immediately.
Furthermore, if you stray
farther than 50 meters from me,
it will explode.
It would be difficult
to wipe your asses without your arms.
Let's go, all five of you!
Fifty meters?
We're supposed to run?
Wait up! Hey!
All right, we'll split up here
and start the search.
The grassy area there is a marsh.
There could be crocodiles, so watch out!
They wouldn't be here.
Why did you volunteer, Jolyne?
Well, it works well for me.
There are plenty of things
I have to ask you.
About the disc
and about the guy named Pale Snake.
Did you try it out?
Did you read McQueen's disc?
Yes, I gave it a try,
but it made me feel terrible.
It felt as if a stench
was entering my brain.
-Then you haven't noticed.
-What?
The image within the disc
contained clues on Pale Snake's aim.
McQueen.
This disc will suit you.
It's yours now.
This is now your Stand ability.
They're stored in one of
the farm tractor tires?
You saw a bunch of them there?
His aim is to collect the discs.
He was collecting Stand abilities and
memories he stole from other Stand users.
There are dozens of discs.
He has to keep them hidden from
the prison guards and other prisoners.
That's why he has them hidden in a tire.
My father's Star Platinum and memory discs
might be stashed there.
What? Father?
So you're searching
for your father's discs?
Sorry, but I don't know
anything more about him.
I'll look for the tractor from the disc.
A tractor?
There's a good number of them here.
-That shed.
-Right.
Hey! You two seem
to be enjoying yourselves.
You think this is a picnic or something?
You're not searching at all!
No, we were discussing
that shed over there.
We'll go search there.
You made us run after you on purpose.
Who's the one having fun here?
Hold it! Did you mutter something?
Oh, it's nothing.
I swore to run around
like a dog and search.
I don't like her.
Crocodile feces.
I said hold it! You disrespectful bitch!
I'm the guard here!
Oops. That was an accident.
The stick accidentally hit it, right?
What is this sound?
Why is my bracelet beeping?
That wasn't on purpose.
You ran into me.
It won't explode, will it?
That was a bad joke.
Do something about it!
Hey now, stay away from me.
What if it explodes
the moment you come near me?
Hold on.
I said I'm sorry! I'm apologizing!
Watch it! I said don't come near me.
I said, make it stop--
Boom!
Yes! That's what you get!
Eat crocodile shit!
It stopped.
Come on. Don't panic and trip, Ermes.
That sound was a warning.
Right, Mr. Prison Guard?
Dammit…
So that was your ability, huh?
Come on.
There's only a tractor
and bags of flour in here.
There's no point in looking inside.
If this was an easy assignment,
then there was no need for volunteers.
Seriously?
There it is, Jolyne!
It's the same tractor.
That's the same tractor I saw on the disc.
The number is the same too.
STAND NAME: STONE OCEAN
STAND MASTER: JOLYNE CUJOH
The same vehicle number. It says four.
They're inside that tire.
We can get to the discs
if we remove the tire.
Listen up!
We will now sweep the wetlands!
The missing inmates
could have drowned in the waters.
You will go look!
Hey, there's no way
I'm going in the water.
I'm not going.
Let's go!
Guess that vehicle is amphibious.
Give me a break.
Who knows what sort of disease
we'll catch in the wetlands!
What a pain.
Now's our chance.
Let's remove the tire now!
Hey, Jolyne.
Doesn't something seem off?
No, something is definitely wrong.
Yes, if we don't remove the tire now,
we would be separated from the guard.
No, that's not what I mean.
He said, "Five is plenty."
That Warden.
He said five inmates are enough.
but there are six of us!
Jolyne, what could this all mean?
Including you and I…
there's six of us here!
I know there were only
the five of us when we left.
But I wasn't paying attention
to how they looked.
Jolyne, what do you think?
I can't say.
I was fixed on catching up.
But then, everyone's wearing a bracelet.
That's strange.
Were there six of us
right from the start?
Hey, you think this is odd too?
There should've been
only five of us, right?
Can you tell who joined us and when?
No, I could be mistaken.
And it doesn't matter
how many of us there are.
She's been with me the entire time.
I remember her.
She's Atroe.
She gets picked on a lot.
She volunteered to escape the bullying.
Right?
I don't know you.
Hey!
What's going on?
Why is my bracelet beeping?
Crap, mine is too!
-Mine too.
-What the hell? They're all beeping.
We must be nearing the 50-meter limit.
But he can't be that far off.
The guard is gone!
Where did he go?
The ATV is covered in blood.
Why is that?
The bracelet won't stop beeping
because the guard's body
is getting farther away from us.
Did he fall in the water
and being washed away?
Find the guard!
He must be within 50 meters!
This is bad!
Hey.
My bracelet's beeping faster!
No way.
She's dead.
Did the additional person attack?
Is it because we got close to the discs?
Look 50 meters away opposite from
the girl that just exploded!
There he is!
Get near him!
The bracelet will stop beeping
and it won't explode either.
Keep your guard up, Jolyne.
Our enemy is among them.
Someone's a real psycho.
She looks suspicious to me.
The woman with the shaved head.
And Atroe didn't recognize her.
It must be her.
Her Stand ability must have killed him.
We'll kill her before she gets us!
Calm down, Ermes.
Say that the shaved woman is the culprit,
so she was guarding the discs
in the shed since before we got here?
That's what it would mean.
That's impossible.
She's an inmate.
An inmate can't keep watch 24/7.
Jolyne, stand back!
-Something's there!
-What?
Just step back.
Get away from the water!
Ermes.
-Did you see something?
-No.
It was nothing.
But I'm not getting in the marsh anymore.
And Jolyne.
We can't be separated, no matter what.
We don't know who the enemy is.
Right. And these bracelets
complicate things.
To take the discs from the shed,
we must be within 50 meters of the guard
and the other three inmates.
Ermes!
Something's in the bucket!
My face got sucked in!
What is this plankton-looking thing?
What?
It split into two.
No, four!
These creatures…
The bucket wasn't empty.
I didn't look hard enough.
They were already in the water.
Smack!
Ermes!
Jolyne, don't come in!
The water is not safe!
They're multiplying!
They can rapidly multiply.
Get out of the water.
You won't make it in time.
I fell into the Stand's trap.
Stone Ocean!
I'll get him now.
Jolyne.
You're walking on the thread?
Doesn't that mean
you're unraveling your own body?
Jolyne, stay away!
I'll take care of myself!
This is crazy!
It's true.
Yes, it's pretty crazy.
Good grief.
I would've been toast
if I hadn't unraveled so much thread.
So this is your power.
Her body has a hole in it.
She let him punch her
so she could grab onto him.
Jolyne, get out of the water now.
Don't stand up, Ermes!
That thing.
It's a bunch of small Stands
clustered together!
It hid inside the tiny bit
of water in the bucket,
and it dragged me in!
I know that.
So don't stand up.
Grab it underwater.
The thread that I'm releasing!
It's fast.
It's powerful too, but its speed...
Just what is it?
A Stand's speed and power should weaken…
the farther it separates from its user.
It got me!
Stay calm, Jolyne.
I put my sticker on it.
When I was caught in its arms earlier.
This is my Stand ability.
I'll peel it off now!
Run further inland!
It's not coming onto land.
Seems it only attacks in the water.
Please respond!
This is inmate FE32125.
This is an emergency.
The guard got in an accident.
Send help immediately!
What happened to you two?
It looked like you were running on water…
You three, don't take another step!
Step away from the water!
Don't try to pull anything on us.
I know one of you did this!
In order to obtain the discs,
it seems we have to defeat the User first.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter